Didin nur yahya

Fullstack Engineer

- +6281413309326
- http://didinnuryahya.herokuapp.com/
- Tangerang, Banten

SUMMARY

Well-qualified Full Stack Developer familiar with wide range of programming utilities and languages. Knowledgeable of backend and frontend development requirements. Handles any part of process with ease. Collaborative team player with excellent technical abilities offering 4 years of related experience.

EXPERIENCE

Test Engineer Intern 08/2022 - Present

Shipper

Reviewed, evaluated and identified requirements for testability.

Analyzed test results and prepared system-level evaluation reports to verify and validate system performance.

Created comprehensive test plans, test scripts and use cases to support testing objectives.

Provided technical advice to improve quality of engineering practices.

Functional Test Atoor Application Using Jira, Testrail and Checking GraphQL & Tracker system function in Frontend application.

Blackbox testing API service in Atoor Platfrom (OCMS marketplace)

Fullstack Engineer 03/2019 - Present

Self Employed Freelance

Develop Web Company Profile For CV Berkah Teknik

Develop Blog Application bucin4lyfeid using SQLite and Python Django

Develop Inventory Application Using Laravel and Mysql For School

Develop MoneyQu Mobile apps Using Flutter and Laravel(Current on-going project)

QA Engineer Intern 01/2022 - 02/2022

Vision+

Created plans and communicated deadlines to complete projects on time.

Proved successful working within tight deadlines and fast-paced atmosphere.

Used coordination and planning skills to achieve results according to schedule.

Used critical thinking to break down problems, evaluate solutions and make decisions.

Backend Engineer 12/2020 - 03/2021

Heylawedu

Develop API Backend service for law education platform heylawedu.id using Laravel, MySQL, Redis, AWS S3 and Digital ocean as cloud service

Backend developer Intern 11/2020 - 12/2020

Bangbeli.com

Develop Web and API Admin for Bangbeli fintech platform

Backend Developer 06/2020 - 08/2020

PT Lintas Telematika Nusantara

Develop API Mobile duniamurah.com

Develop Backoffice application duniamurah.com

Develop API and admin web geraiemas.com

Fullstack Engineer 08/2019 - 12/2019

CV Nagata Inovasi

Developing website kerjapedia.id using laravel, mysql and bootstrap framework

Software Engineer 05/2019 - 08/2019

Kementerian Pendidikan dan Kebudayaan (Ministry of Education and Culture Republic of Indonesia)

Maintenence and develop Module Assesment Exam Application AKSI Using PHP And Javascript ES6

Correct and fixing digital exam in Aksi web application

Data Entry Data National Assesment PISA

Frontend developer 10/2018 - 02/2018

ICRAFT

Develop Web Frontend Qelola with HTML, CSS And Jquery

Fullstack Engineer Intern 01/2018 - 03/2018

PT Bareksa Portal Investasi

Build monitoring server application web based use laravel, Mysql and Bootstrap

EDUCATION

Informatics 2023

Gunadarma Univesity - Bachelor of Engineering

Grade: 3.6

Activities and societies: Final Year StudentActivities and societies: Final Year Student

Programming stack: Assembly, COBOL, Python, Ruby, C#, PHP, Golang

Software engineering 2019

SMK Bina Informatika - Associate of software engineering

Elected Captain of Software Development Team

Professional development completed in Fullstack Java Developer

Received Bina Informatika Scholarship

Awarded Web technologies Student Skills Competition in regional city and province level

CERTIFICATES

Fullstack Java Certification 08/2017 - 12/2017

SKILLS

.....

PHP C# Intermediate Expert Golang Advanced Dart Intermediate Advanced Advanced Javacript Flutter Python Intermediate Java Advanced

Rust Beginner

LANGUAGES

.....

English Intermediate Indonesia Native